[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Do you think America is more or less racist since the inauguration of the first black president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "I think what Barack Obama is going through (INAUDIBLE) than race.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Do they know what they're protesting about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "Well, nobody has put a fine point on it but it's not hard to see why people might be outraged by Wall Street.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harrisburg"]}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Now when whole towns in America starts declaring themselves bankrupt, this is a sign that this is pretty serious, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Yes, but I'm not sure what the bankruptcy of Harrisburg means.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "But is America basically bust financially?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, America has been living beyond its means for a generation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "And where do you see this politically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "So you've got to accept that -- like everyone else in the world when I answer that question, I'm just guessing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Why did you go looking for whatever it was you found?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "There were a couple of reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "I mean when you have monks who are behaving like this, hasn't the whole world basically lost its entire moral compass?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, you know, you probably give monks too much credit just to start with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "So I'll tell you after I'm done, how about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "RP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "Well, I hope you come back on and talk to me about it when it's done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Is that a deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Thanks for having me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin Luther King"], "LOCATION": ["Harlem"]}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "If I had that power, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "The first time I met Martin Luther King in the basement of a church in Harlem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Humble, without false modesty, eloquent, intellectual, extremely intellectual and highly intelligent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "How far do you think America has come in realizing Martin Luther King's dream?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "There's no question we have realized a good portion of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin Luther King"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Do you see that anymore in modern leaders?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "No, I do not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "How did you feel when he got elected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I had hoped very much that he would be that person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Do you think America is more or less racist since the inauguration of the first black president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Certainly the amount of social activism, we are less racist than appearance.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What did you think when he said that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I subscribed to it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What did you feel when that happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I felt that something very important had been revealed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Or do you wish you had never sung the damn thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I'm glad I sung it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What are your personal other favorite songs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "\"Try to Remember,\" a great ballad from the Fantastics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Did you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What was your view of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Like many, I was certainly in awe of his great gift and his talent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Or in the end, do you yourself have to do with these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I think, along the way, there are individuals that intervene that help you to see a brighter side to things and can help -- you can trust their view of what they say about you and the distortions you may be living through.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111013pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "When you look back, how would you like to be remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "There are two things that have defined me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]